Zhang Qin
張沁
Are you crazy
你瘋了嗎你
I really thought you weren't afraid of death
我還真以為你不怕死呢
You crazy person
你這個瘋子
Are you crazy
你瘋了嗎你
How could the Zhang family allow
張家怎麼容許
you, a lunatic, to run wild
你這個瘋子撒野
My Zhang family’s daughter
我張家的女兒
When will it be your turn to interrupt?
什麼時候輪到你插嘴了
But isn’t she just a
但她不就是個
Goddaughter?
乾女兒嗎
Who told you that she is a goddaughter?
誰告訴你是乾女兒了
Don't forget
你別忘了
Her surname is Zhang
她姓張
Do you really think that
你們該不會真以為
our Zhang family
我們張家
will find someone casually
會隨便找個人
to inherit our family business
來繼承我們家業吧
Back then
當初
She insisted on marrying
她執意要嫁給
you, a little beast
你這個小畜生
That's why she left the Zhang family
才離開了張家
As a result
結果
you just think she is an
你們就當她是個
orphan without parents
無父無母的孤兒